

ENZO GABRIEL SCHIAVONI Electromechanical engineer

SUMMARY

I am a 25 year old Argentinean, recently graduated, eager to gain experience in my field as an electromechanical engineer. I am currently living in Germany and have a visa that allows me to work in the country. I am a person that always wonders about how things work and that doesn't give up easily when solving problems.

EDUCATION

Universidad Nacional de La Pampa / Instituto Balseiro - Argentina - (2013-2019)

Electromechanical engineering major oriented to industrial installations, electric, mechanic, thermal and hydraulic machines.

In the last semester of the degree I attended classes in Instituto Balseiro, where I used physical system identification methods and control theory to design a self balancing robot ("Implementing a self balancing robot") (thesis grade: 1,6). Besides I had the opportunity to program a robotic arm where the goal was to manipulate objects using computer vision ("Robotic arm using computer vision").

ESCUELA NORMAL MIXTA - ARGENTINA - (2010-2012)

Secondary school oriented to Natural Science. (GPA: 1.86).

WORK EXPERIENCE

Working Holiday Visa Program - Ireland (Sep 2019 - Aug 2020)

With the goal to improve my language skills and learning about other cultures, I applied to an Irish visa that allowed me to live and work there for one year. In that period I worked in different places such as in a mechanical garage and on a farm.

Universidad Nacional de La Pampa - Argentina - (Aug 2016 - Feb 2018)

Teacher assistant in Physics. I helped students with practice and theory.

TECNOMOTOR JP - ARGENTINA - (FEB 2012 - FEB 2018)

Assistant in an automobile workshop, where I learned about electronic fuel injection and automotive mechanics.

SKILLS

- Software: Solidworks, Autocad, Simulink, Matlab, C programming, PLC programming, MPLAB, Proteus
- Languages: English: professional working proficiency. Spanish: native speaker

CONTACT

- Email/Tel: enzoschiavoni95@gmail.com / +353899815611
- Address: Ferdinand Scholling Ring 13, Frankfurt am Main, Germany